If you're not willing to hold the candidates that you want to win to any standard of ethics,
then I don't know what you think they're going to do when they win.
Because you've already shown them that they can just do the opposite of what you have demanded of them and still get your support.
Now, for the record, y'all know I don't even believe in electoral politics.
What I do believe in is the people.
And it is quite disheartening to watch people who I know are smart, who I know are principled,
continuously fall prey to establishment politics.
Instead of demanding that the folks that they support be deeply and solidly against capitulating to it.
Get your energy right.
Come and join me, Amanda Seals, this Wednesday, August 12th,
and every second Wednesday at Comedy in Harlem for Radical Rhythms Experience.
Every month we come together to level up our vibration with music, humor, and each other.
Tickets available at ComedyinHarlem.com.